JORY DURHAM

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER







323-434-5084

jorydurham@icloud.com

https://jorydurham-portfolio.netlify.app/

Profile

Passionate and self-driving developer pursuing to launch a career in front-end web development. Knowledgeable in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Experienced working with different web applications. Exceptional eve for detail with excellent communication and teamwork skills.

Education

2022-2023

ZERO TO MASTERY

ZTM is an online course used to become a self-taught full stack web developer. Gained experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES6-2022), Node.js, React, and PostgresSQL.

2016-2017

MASTER'S UNIVERSITY

Santa Clarita, CA

Awards & **Qualifications**

- Secret Security Clearance
- Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal (2)
- Cyber Awareness and Essentials

Experience

2018-2023 US Navy

DAMAGE CONTROLMEN (E-5)

Organized and lead ten man fire teams in life threatening emergencies. Supervised and scheduled maintenance on life saving equipment equating to over 25,000 manhours and trained over 200 personnel in advanced firefighting. Planned, prepared, and presented over six major inspections directly resulting in the USS America (LHA-6) Battle Ready Certification and Qualification.

JAN 2017- SEP 2017

New Power

SALES REPRESENTITIVE

Learned and developed exceptional communication and teamwork skills, Ensured current customers had the right product and services, identified new markets and customer leads, and pitched to prospective customers. Gained excellent time management and customer relations skills, trained new sales representatives and supervised six other team members.

Skills

- HTML5 (ES6-2022) & CSS Training and Development
- JavaScript
- **Event Planning**

Microsoft Excel

- React
 - Node.js
- PostgresSQL

Reference

Heru Mansell

Commander, US Navy

Email: heru.mansell@lha6.navy.mil

Manny Prado

Captain, US Navy

Email: manny.pardo@lha6.navy.mil